getliner.com 2019-05-07

# None

**Privacy Policy**

 **Privacy Policy**

LINER provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use, disclosure and protection of information that apply to our Service, as well as your choices regarding the collection and use of information.

LINER provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use, disclosure and protection of information that apply to our Service, as well as your choices regarding the collection and use of information.

2\. Peesonally Identifiable Information

2\. Peesonally Identifiable Information

To use the LINER servioe, an email address, username and password are required. We use personally identifiable information to deliver the Service, to comply with reasonable requests of law enforcement and recommend additional content to you.

To use the LINER servioe, an email address, username and password are required. We use personally identifiable information to deliver the Service, to comply with reasonable requests of law enforcement and recommend additional content to you.

Where applicable, we indicate whether and why you must provide us with your Personal Information, as well as the consequences of failing to do so. If you do not provide Personal Information when requested, you may not be able to benefit from our Service if that information is necessary to provide you with the service or if we are legally required to collect it.

Where applicable, we indicate whether and why you must provide us with your Personal Information, as well as the consequences of failing to do so. If you do not provide Personal Information when requested, you may not be able to benefit from our Service if that information is necessary to provide you with the service or if we are legally required to collect it.

* Personally identifiable information provided by you
* Personally identifiable information provided by you

Registration: If you desire to have access to certain restricted sections of the Site or request to receive marketing materials, you may be required to become a registered user, and to submit the following types of Personal Information to LINER: your name, email address, user name, password, city, and time zone.

Registration: If you desire to have access to certain restricted sections of the Site or request to receive marketing materials, you may be required to become a registered user, and to submit the following types of Personal Information to LINER: your name, email address, user name, password, city, and time zone.

Customer Support: We may collect information through your communications with our customer support team or other communications that you may send us and their contents.

Customer Support: We may collect information through your communications with our customer support team or other communications that you may send us and their contents.

Making a Purchase: When you make payments through the Service, you will need to provide Personal Information such as your credit card number and billing address.

Making a Purchase: When you make payments through the Service, you will need to provide Personal Information such as your credit card number and billing address.

Other: We may also collect your contact details when you provide them in the context of our customer, vendor, and partner relationships.

Other: We may also collect your contact details when you provide them in the context of our customer, vendor, and partner relationships.

3\. Non-Personally Identifiable Information

3\. Non-Personally Identifiable Information

We also collect and use information about your interactions with the Service in a manner and format that does not identify you as an individual (“Non-Personally Identifiable Information”). We may collect, use, and disclose Non-Personally Identifiable Information as set forth below.

We also collect and use information about your interactions with the Service in a manner and format that does not identify you as an individual (“Non-Personally Identifiable Information”). We may collect, use, and disclose Non-Personally Identifiable Information as set forth below.

We collect information about the URLs, titles, highlights, comments and other information you save to LINER. The types of information we collect includes your browser type, device type, time zone, language, and other information related to the manner in which you access LINER. If you are on a mobile device, we may collect the advertising identifiers provided by Apple on iOS and by Google on Android. You can change this identifier in your device settings. We also collect information about your use of LINER so that we can provide our services. For example, as a part of providing LINER’s syncing features, we sync information about the items that you save and view within LINER so that your article list, color order, and other account and usage information may be synced across all of your devices.

We collect information about the URLs, titles, highlights, comments and other information you save to LINER. The types of information we collect includes your browser type, device type, time zone, language, and other information related to the manner in which you access LINER. If you are on a mobile device, we may collect the advertising identifiers provided by Apple on iOS and by Google on Android. You can change this identifier in your device settings. We also collect information about your use of LINER so that we can provide our services. For example, as a part of providing LINER’s syncing features, we sync information about the items that you save and view within LINER so that your article list, color order, and other account and usage information may be synced across all of your devices.

* Non-Personally identifiable information provided by you
* Non-Personally identifiable information provided by you

Analytics Information: We use third-party analytics tools to help us measure traffic and usage trends for the Service. These tools collect information sent by your application as part of a page request and other information that assists us in improving the Service. We collect and use this analytics information in aggregate form such that it cannot reasonably be manipulated to identify any particular individual user.

Analytics Information: We use third-party analytics tools to help us measure traffic and usage trends for the Service. These tools collect information sent by your application as part of a page request and other information that assists us in improving the Service. We collect and use this analytics information in aggregate form such that it cannot reasonably be manipulated to identify any particular individual user.

Log File Information: When you use our Service, our servers automatically record certain log file information to automatically add hhlights to the web page. These server logs may include anonymous information such as your web request, device type and other information related to highlights.

Log File Information: When you use our Service, our servers automatically record certain log file information to automatically add hhlights to the web page. These server logs may include anonymous information such as your web request, device type and other information related to highlights.

Cookies and Similar Technologies: Like many websites, we also use “cookie” technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve the Site and our Service. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk. A session cookie enables certain features of the Site and our service and is deleted from your computer when you disconnect from or leave the Site. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. LINER may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with the Site and our Service, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on the Site, and to improve the Site and our Service.

Cookies and Similar Technologies: Like many websites, we also use “cookie” technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve the Site and our Service. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk. A session cookie enables certain features of the Site and our service and is deleted from your computer when you disconnect from or leave the Site. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. LINER may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with the Site and our Service, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on the Site, and to improve the Site and our Service.

We may also automatically record certain information from your device by using various types of technology, including “clear gifs” or “web beacons.” This automatically collected information may include your IP address or other device address or ID, web browser and/or device type, the web pages or sites that you visit just before or just after you use the Service, the pages or other content you view or otherwise interact with on the Service, and the dates and times that you visit, access, or use the Service. We also may use these technologies to collect information regarding your interaction with email messages, such as whether you opened, clicked on, or forwarded a message, to the extent permitted under applicable law.

We may also automatically record certain information from your device by using various types of technology, including “clear gifs” or “web beacons.” This automatically collected information may include your IP address or other device address or ID, web browser and/or device type, the web pages or sites that you visit just before or just after you use the Service, the pages or other content you view or otherwise interact with on the Service, and the dates and times that you visit, access, or use the Service. We also may use these technologies to collect information regarding your interaction with email messages, such as whether you opened, clicked on, or forwarded a message, to the extent permitted under applicable law.

You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. Please note that if you delete, or choose not to accept, cookies from the Service, you may not be able to utilize the features of the Service to their fullest potential.

You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. Please note that if you delete, or choose not to accept, cookies from the Service, you may not be able to utilize the features of the Service to their fullest potential.

Third Party Web Beacons and Third Party Buttons: Third-party content may use cookies, web beacons, or other mechanisms for obtaining data in connection with your viewing of the third party content on the Service. Additionally, we may implement third party buttons, such as Facebook “share” buttons, that may function as web beacons even when you do not interact with the button. Information collected through third-party web beacons and buttons is collected directly by these third parties, not by LINER. Please consult such third party’s data collection, use, and disclosure policies for more information.

Third Party Web Beacons and Third Party Buttons: Third-party content may use cookies, web beacons, or other mechanisms for obtaining data in connection with your viewing of the third party content on the Service. Additionally, we may implement third party buttons, such as Facebook “share” buttons, that may function as web beacons even when you do not interact with the button. Information collected through third-party web beacons and buttons is collected directly by these third parties, not by LINER. Please consult such third party’s data collection, use, and disclosure policies for more information.

Links to Other Websites: Our Site contains links to other websites. The fact that we link to a website is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit Personal Information from you. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the Personal Information you submit to them. We are not responsible for the content, privacy and security practices, and policies of third-party sites or services to which links or access are provided through the Service. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.

Links to Other Websites: Our Site contains links to other websites. The fact that we link to a website is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit Personal Information from you. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the Personal Information you submit to them. We are not responsible for the content, privacy and security practices, and policies of third-party sites or services to which links or access are provided through the Service. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.

4\. How We May Use Your Personal Information

4\. How We May Use Your Personal Information

We use your personal information to respond to your requests and perform our contract with you. We may do this, for example, by using your contact information to respond to your inquiries, to provide customer support and to supply any products or services you have requested. In addition, if you choose to use LINER to share content with another person, we will use the recipient's email address or user account information to provide that service, but we will not use that email address for any other purpose.

We use your personal information to respond to your requests and perform our contract with you. We may do this, for example, by using your contact information to respond to your inquiries, to provide customer support and to supply any products or services you have requested. In addition, if you choose to use LINER to share content with another person, we will use the recipient's email address or user account information to provide that service, but we will not use that email address for any other purpose.

We also have a legitimate business interest to operate and improve our services such as saving articles, highlights, comments, or other content to LINER and making such content and recommendations available to you at a later time on any device that you use to access LINER. We also use non-identifying, aggregated information to analyze the manner in which LINER is used, which also allows us to improve our services. The aggregated information we use includes the manner in which articles, highlights, comments, or content has been accessed, saved and shared. We may use aggregated information to offer a list of top sites or content, to make recommendations to our users, to report on usage and trends, to improve the products and services that we offer, or to develop new products and services.

We also have a legitimate business interest to operate and improve our services such as saving articles, highlights, comments, or other content to LINER and making such content and recommendations available to you at a later time on any device that you use to access LINER. We also use non-identifying, aggregated information to analyze the manner in which LINER is used, which also allows us to improve our services. The aggregated information we use includes the manner in which articles, highlights, comments, or content has been accessed, saved and shared. We may use aggregated information to offer a list of top sites or content, to make recommendations to our users, to report on usage and trends, to improve the products and services that we offer, or to develop new products and services.

We also may use the Personal Information we obtain about you to:

We also may use the Personal Information we obtain about you to:

* create and manage your account, provide our Service, process payments, and respond to your inquiries;
* create and manage your account, provide our Service, process payments, and respond to your inquiries;

* communicate with you to verify your account and for informational and operational purposes, such as account management, customer service, or system maintenance, including by periodically emailing you service-related announcements;
* communicate with you to verify your account and for informational and operational purposes, such as account management, customer service, or system maintenance, including by periodically emailing you service-related announcements;

* tailor our Service (e.g., we may use cookies and similar technologies to remember your preferences);
* tailor our Service (e.g., we may use cookies and similar technologies to remember your preferences);

* aggregate your Personal Information for analytical purposes;
* aggregate your Personal Information for analytical purposes;

* provide customer support;
* provide customer support;

* operate, evaluate and improve our business (including by developing new products and services; managing our communications; analyzing how the Service is being accessed and used; tracking performance of the Service; debugging the Service; facilitating the use of our Service);
* operate, evaluate and improve our business (including by developing new products and services; managing our communications; analyzing how the Service is being accessed and used; tracking performance of the Service; debugging the Service; facilitating the use of our Service);

* send you marketing communications about products, services, offers, programs and promotions of LINER, and affiliated companies;
* send you marketing communications about products, services, offers, programs and promotions of LINER, and affiliated companies;

* ensure the security of our Service;
* ensure the security of our Service;

* manage our customer, service provider and partner relationships;
* manage our customer, service provider and partner relationships;

* enforce our agreements related to our Service and our other legal rights; and
* enforce our agreements related to our Service and our other legal rights; and

* comply with applicable legal requirements, industry standards and our policies.
* comply with applicable legal requirements, industry standards and our policies.

If you are located in the European Economic Area, we may process your Personal Information for the above purposes when:

If you are located in the European Economic Area, we may process your Personal Information for the above purposes when:

* you have consented to the use of your Personal Information, For example, we may seek to obtain your consent for our uses of cookies or similar technologies, or to send you marketing communications.
* you have consented to the use of your Personal Information, For example, we may seek to obtain your consent for our uses of cookies or similar technologies, or to send you marketing communications.

* we need your Personal Information to provide you with services and products requested by you, or to respond to your inquiries,
* we need your Personal Information to provide you with services and products requested by you, or to respond to your inquiries,

* we have a legal obligation to use your Personal Information, or
* we have a legal obligation to use your Personal Information, or

* we have a legitimate interest in using your Personal Information. In particular, we have a legitimate interest in using your Personal Information to ensure and improve the safety, security, and performance of our Service, to anonymize Personal Information and carry out data analyses.
* we have a legitimate interest in using your Personal Information. In particular, we have a legitimate interest in using your Personal Information to ensure and improve the safety, security, and performance of our Service, to anonymize Personal Information and carry out data analyses.

5\. How We Share Your Personal Information

5\. How We Share Your Personal Information

We may disclose the Personal Information we collect about you as described below or otherwise disclosed to you at the time the data is collected, including with:

We may disclose the Personal Information we collect about you as described below or otherwise disclosed to you at the time the data is collected, including with:

Service Providers: We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us, including hosting and maintenance, error monitoring, debugging, performance monitoring, billing, customer relationship, database storage and management, and direct marketing campaigns. We may share your Personal Information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services. We also require these third parties to maintain the privacy and security of the Personal Information they process on our behalf.

Service Providers: We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us, including hosting and maintenance, error monitoring, debugging, performance monitoring, billing, customer relationship, database storage and management, and direct marketing campaigns. We may share your Personal Information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services. We also require these third parties to maintain the privacy and security of the Personal Information they process on our behalf.

Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement: LINER cooperates with government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law. To the extent permitted under applicable law, we may disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we believe is necessary or appropriate to investigate, respond to, and defend against claims, for legal process (including subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of LINER or a third party, to protect LINER against liability, for the safety of the public or any person, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, fraudulent, abusive, or legally actionable activity, to protect the security or integrity of the Service and any equipment used to make the Service available, or to comply with the law.

Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement: LINER cooperates with government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law. To the extent permitted under applicable law, we may disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we believe is necessary or appropriate to investigate, respond to, and defend against claims, for legal process (including subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of LINER or a third party, to protect LINER against liability, for the safety of the public or any person, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, fraudulent, abusive, or legally actionable activity, to protect the security or integrity of the Service and any equipment used to make the Service available, or to comply with the law.

Business Transfers: LINER may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization, sale of assets, or similar transaction, or in the event of insolvency or bankruptcy. You will have the opportunity to opt out of any such transfer if the new entity’s planned processing of your information differs materially from that set forth in this Privacy Policy.

Business Transfers: LINER may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization, sale of assets, or similar transaction, or in the event of insolvency or bankruptcy. You will have the opportunity to opt out of any such transfer if the new entity’s planned processing of your information differs materially from that set forth in this Privacy Policy.

Other Third Parties: We may share Personal Information with our headquarters and affiliates, and business partners to whom it is reasonably necessary or desirable for us to disclose your data for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. We may also make certain non-Personal Information available to third parties for various purposes, including for business or marketing purposes or to assist third parties in understanding our users’ interest, habits, and usage patterns for certain programs, content, services, advertisements, promotions, and functionality available through the Service.

Other Third Parties: We may share Personal Information with our headquarters and affiliates, and business partners to whom it is reasonably necessary or desirable for us to disclose your data for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. We may also make certain non-Personal Information available to third parties for various purposes, including for business or marketing purposes or to assist third parties in understanding our users’ interest, habits, and usage patterns for certain programs, content, services, advertisements, promotions, and functionality available through the Service.

6\. How We Protect Your Personal Information

6\. How We Protect Your Personal Information

LINER is very concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your Personal Information. We employ administrative and electronic measures designed to appropriately protect your Personal Information against accidental or unlawful destruction, accidental loss, unauthorized alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access, misuse, and any other unlawful form of processing of the Personal Information in our possession. Please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot guarantee that information about you will not be accessed, viewed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our administrative, physical, and electronic safeguards, subject to requirements under applicable law to ensure or warrant information security.

LINER is very concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your Personal Information. We employ administrative and electronic measures designed to appropriately protect your Personal Information against accidental or unlawful destruction, accidental loss, unauthorized alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access, misuse, and any other unlawful form of processing of the Personal Information in our possession. Please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot guarantee that information about you will not be accessed, viewed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our administrative, physical, and electronic safeguards, subject to requirements under applicable law to ensure or warrant information security.

We will make any legally-required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored Personal Information to you via email or conspicuous posting on our Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system, and any other disclosures that may be required under applicable law.

We will make any legally-required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored Personal Information to you via email or conspicuous posting on our Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system, and any other disclosures that may be required under applicable law.

We also take measures to delete your Personal Information or keep it in a form that does not permit identifying you when this information is no longer necessary for the purposes for which we process it, unless we are required by law to keep this information for a longer period. When determining the retention period, we take into account various criteria, such as the type of products and services requested by or provided to you, the nature and length of our relationship with you, possible re-enrollment with our products or services, the impact on the services we provide to you if we delete some information from or about you, mandatory retention periods provided by law and the statute of limitations.

We also take measures to delete your Personal Information or keep it in a form that does not permit identifying you when this information is no longer necessary for the purposes for which we process it, unless we are required by law to keep this information for a longer period. When determining the retention period, we take into account various criteria, such as the type of products and services requested by or provided to you, the nature and length of our relationship with you, possible re-enrollment with our products or services, the impact on the services we provide to you if we delete some information from or about you, mandatory retention periods provided by law and the statute of limitations.

7\. Your Rights and Choices

7\. Your Rights and Choices

If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such marketing communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications. You may also opt out from receiving commercial email from us by sending your request to us by email at privacy@getliner.com. Please be aware that, even after you opt out from receiving commercial messages from us, you will continue to receive administrative messages from us regarding the Service.

If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such marketing communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications. You may also opt out from receiving commercial email from us by sending your request to us by email at privacy@getliner.com. Please be aware that, even after you opt out from receiving commercial messages from us, you will continue to receive administrative messages from us regarding the Service.

In certain jurisdictions you have the right to request access and receive information about the Personal Information we maintain about you, to update and correct inaccuracies in your Personal Information, to restrict or object to the processing of your Personal Information, to have the information blocked, anonymized or deleted, as appropriate, or to exercise your right to data portability to transfer your Personal Information to another company. Those rights may be limited in some circumstances by local law requirements. In addition to the above-mentioned rights, you also have the right to lodge a complaint with a competent supervisory authority subject to applicable law.

In certain jurisdictions you have the right to request access and receive information about the Personal Information we maintain about you, to update and correct inaccuracies in your Personal Information, to restrict or object to the processing of your Personal Information, to have the information blocked, anonymized or deleted, as appropriate, or to exercise your right to data portability to transfer your Personal Information to another company. Those rights may be limited in some circumstances by local law requirements. In addition to the above-mentioned rights, you also have the right to lodge a complaint with a competent supervisory authority subject to applicable law.

Where required by law, we obtain your consent for the processing of certain Personal Information collected by cookies or similar technologies, or used to send you direct marketing communications, or when we carry out other processing activities for which consent may be required. If we rely on consent for the processing of your Personal Information, you have the right to withdraw it at any time and free of charge. When you do so, this will not affect the lawfulness of the processing before your consent withdrawal.

Where required by law, we obtain your consent for the processing of certain Personal Information collected by cookies or similar technologies, or used to send you direct marketing communications, or when we carry out other processing activities for which consent may be required. If we rely on consent for the processing of your Personal Information, you have the right to withdraw it at any time and free of charge. When you do so, this will not affect the lawfulness of the processing before your consent withdrawal.

To update your preferences, ask us to remove your information from our mailing lists, delete your account or submit a request to exercise your rights under applicable law, please contact us as specified in the “How to Contact Us” section below.

To update your preferences, ask us to remove your information from our mailing lists, delete your account or submit a request to exercise your rights under applicable law, please contact us as specified in the “How to Contact Us” section below.

8\. Data Transfers

8\. Data Transfers

LINER(Aurum Planet Co., Ltd.) is based in the Republic of Korea. Personal Information that we collect may be transferred to, and stored at, any of our affiliates, partners or service providers which may be inside or outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”) and Switzerland, including the Republic of Korea. By submitting your personal data, you agree to such transfers. Your Personal Information may be transferred to countries that do not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you initially provided the information. When we transfer or disclose your Personal Information to other countries, we will protect that information as described in this Privacy Policy.

LINER(Aurum Planet Co., Ltd.) is based in the Republic of Korea. Personal Information that we collect may be transferred to, and stored at, any of our affiliates, partners or service providers which may be inside or outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”) and Switzerland, including the Republic of Korea. By submitting your personal data, you agree to such transfers. Your Personal Information may be transferred to countries that do not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you initially provided the information. When we transfer or disclose your Personal Information to other countries, we will protect that information as described in this Privacy Policy.

9\. Children’s Privacy

9\. Children’s Privacy

The Site is not directed to persons under 16. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at privacy@getliner.com. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under 16. If we become aware that a child under 16 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files.

The Site is not directed to persons under 16. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at privacy@getliner.com. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under 16. If we become aware that a child under 16 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files.

10\. Updates to This Privacy Policy

10\. Updates to This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason; each version will apply to information collected while it was in place. We will notify you of any modifications to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy on our Site and indicating the date of the latest revision. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes.

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason; each version will apply to information collected while it was in place. We will notify you of any modifications to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy on our Site and indicating the date of the latest revision. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes.

In the event that the modifications materially alter your rights or obligations hereunder, we will make reasonable efforts to notify you of the change. For example, we may send a message to your email address or generate a pop-up or similar notification when you access the Service for the first time after such material changes are made. Your continued use of the Service after the revised Privacy Policy has become effective indicates that you have read, understood and agreed to the current version of this Privacy Policy.

In the event that the modifications materially alter your rights or obligations hereunder, we will make reasonable efforts to notify you of the change. For example, we may send a message to your email address or generate a pop-up or similar notification when you access the Service for the first time after such material changes are made. Your continued use of the Service after the revised Privacy Policy has become effective indicates that you have read, understood and agreed to the current version of this Privacy Policy.

11\. Referral Service and Requesting References

11\. Referral Service and Requesting References

LINER provides a referral service that allows you to invite your friends and contacts to use LINER. We may integrate the Platform with third party sites such as Facebook, so that you can send invitation messages or requests for references via the third party site itself.

LINER provides a referral service that allows you to invite your friends and contacts to use LINER. We may integrate the Platform with third party sites such as Facebook, so that you can send invitation messages or requests for references via the third party site itself.

You may also send invitation/request emails via the Platform itself, in which case we will ask you for the contact information to which to send your invitation/request. You can type in the email addresses or other contact information manually, or you can choose to import the contacts in your address book(s). In both cases, we may use and store this information for the sole purposes of allowing you to send your friends and contacts an invitation or request for a reference, and for fraud detection and prevention. With respect to referrals, we will also store the email addresses of your invitees to track if your friend joins LINER in response to your referral.

You may also send invitation/request emails via the Platform itself, in which case we will ask you for the contact information to which to send your invitation/request. You can type in the email addresses or other contact information manually, or you can choose to import the contacts in your address book(s). In both cases, we may use and store this information for the sole purposes of allowing you to send your friends and contacts an invitation or request for a reference, and for fraud detection and prevention. With respect to referrals, we will also store the email addresses of your invitees to track if your friend joins LINER in response to your referral.

12\. GDPR Compliance

12\. GDPR Compliance

The EU’s General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR) take effect May 25, and we are fully behind the spirit of these regulations for a safe and secure Internet. We aspire to embrace privacy by design and, whenever possible, to not collect and store personally-identifiable information.

The EU’s General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR) take effect May 25, and we are fully behind the spirit of these regulations for a safe and secure Internet. We aspire to embrace privacy by design and, whenever possible, to not collect and store personally-identifiable information.

Our Privacy Policy contains mentions of the few instances where personally-identifiable information is required. Typically this will include an email address in order to log in to LINER or a social network username in order to manage your account.

Our Privacy Policy contains mentions of the few instances where personally-identifiable information is required. Typically this will include an email address in order to log in to LINER or a social network username in order to manage your account.

Overall, we aim for privacy by default: if data collection is not integral to the way our product works, then we won’t collect it. This approach has felt very much in line with the spirit of GDPR, and we’re fortunate that a lot of these data collection practices have been in place at LINER for some time. As such, you may see few banners or forms requesting consent for us to collect personally-identifiable information for tracking or other purposes. We don’t deem this information necessary to provide LINER’s service to you, and we choose not to engage in activities and strategies that make this data relevant.

Overall, we aim for privacy by default: if data collection is not integral to the way our product works, then we won’t collect it. This approach has felt very much in line with the spirit of GDPR, and we’re fortunate that a lot of these data collection practices have been in place at LINER for some time. As such, you may see few banners or forms requesting consent for us to collect personally-identifiable information for tracking or other purposes. We don’t deem this information necessary to provide LINER’s service to you, and we choose not to engage in activities and strategies that make this data relevant.

At any time, you may request your information to be exported and sent to you for review, and we promptly honor any requests by you to have your information deleted and forgotten.

At any time, you may request your information to be exported and sent to you for review, and we promptly honor any requests by you to have your information deleted and forgotten.

13\. How to Contact Us

13\. How to Contact Us

We have appointed a data protection officer (DPO) for the LINER who is responsible for overseeing questions in relation to this privacy notice. If you have any questions, concerns, or requests about this privacy notice, how we manage your personal Information, or any other issue relating to your personal Information, please contact our DPO:

We have appointed a data protection officer (DPO) for the LINER who is responsible for overseeing questions in relation to this privacy notice. If you have any questions, concerns, or requests about this privacy notice, how we manage your personal Information, or any other issue relating to your personal Information, please contact our DPO:

Aurum Planet Co., Ltd.

Aurum Planet Co., Ltd.

Attn: Data Protection Officer

Attn: Data Protection Officer

Email: privacy@getliner.com

Email: privacy@getliner.com

Address: 3F, 53, World Cup buk-ro 6-gil, Mapo-gu, Seoul, Republic of Korea (Zip Code: 03991)

Address: 3F, 53, World Cup buk-ro 6-gil, Mapo-gu, Seoul, Republic of Korea (Zip Code: 03991)

Telephone number: +82 70 4110 1555

Telephone number: +82 70 4110 1555

Last modified: 1 Sep, 2018.

Last modified: 1 Sep, 2018.

Effective: 5 Sep, 2018.

Effective: 5 Sep, 2018.
